=Misfeeling=
=سوء الشعور=
=Episode 1=
=الحلقة 1=
(Lu Chengbei,)
(لو تشينغبي،)
(Meng Xunmei,)
(منغ شونمي،)
(do you know how important)
(هل تعرف مدى أهمية)
(Engagement: Lu Chengbei &amp; Meng Xunmei) (you are to me?)
(الخطوبة: Lu Chengbei & Meng Xunmei) (أنت بالنسبة لي؟)
(My hatred towards you)
(كرهي لك)
(was never buried.)
(لم يدفن قط).
(Even if the truth is destroyed,)
(حتى لو تم تدمير الحق)
(it is destined to resurface,)
(ومن المقرر أن تعود إلى السطح،)
(like a phoenix reborn)
(مثل طائر الفينيق الذي ولد من جديد)
(from the ashes.)
(من الرماد.)
Why hasn't the banquet started yet?
لماذا لم تبدأ المأدبة بعد؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Can't you tell who I am?
ألا تستطيع أن تقول من أنا؟
I'm the bride.
أنا العروس.
You're the bride?
أنت العروس؟
Then who is the one in the banquet hall?
ثم من هو الذي في قاعة المأدبة؟
(Where have you been all these years?)
(أين كنت طوال هذه السنوات؟)
(Don't you know?)
(ألا تعلم؟)
(My disappearance)
(اختفائي)
(was all for this return.)
(كان كل شيء من أجل هذه العودة.)
(Am I dreaming?)
(هل أنا في حلم؟)
(I can actually touch you again.)
(يمكنني في الواقع لمسك مرة أخرى.)
(Your warmth)
(دفئك)
(is so real.)
(هو حقيقي جدا.)
(Lu Chengbei,)
(لو تشينغبي،)
(welcome to my hell.)
(اهلا بك في جحيمي.)
(This)
(هذا)
(is just the beginning.)
(هو مجرد بداية.)
Who are you? Why are you here?
من أنت؟  لماذا أنت هنا؟
Jiang Shiqian?
جيانغ شيكيان؟
Long time no see,
وقت طويل لا رؤية،
old classmate.
زميل قديم.
I told you to leave!
قلت لك أن تغادر!
Hurry up and go out.
اسرع واخرج.
- Let's go, let's go. - Hurry up, can't you hear me?
- لنذهب لنذهب.  - أسرعي، ألا تسمعينني؟
Move.
يتحرك.
(Before meeting you, the world was desolate.)
(قبل لقائك كان العالم مقفرًا).
Childish.
طفولي.
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Thank you, I don't need it.
شكرا لك، أنا لا أحتاج إليها.
I, Lu Chengbei, never take back
أنا، لو تشينغبي، لن أتراجع أبدًا
a gift I give away.
هدية أعطيها بعيدا.
Since it's a gift to me,
وبما أنها هدية لي
then it's mine now.
فهو ملكي الآن.
Can I dispose of it as I please?
هل يمكنني التخلص منها كما يحلو لي؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
(Lu Chengbei,)
(لو تشينغبي،)
(you actually like this type.)
(أنت في الواقع تحب هذا النوع.)
You dance really well.
أنت ترقص بشكل جيد حقا.
No wonder boys at school
لا عجب الأولاد في المدرسة
are chasing after you.
يطاردونك.
Do you have something to say?
هل لديك ما تقوله؟
This place is indeed a nice place to dance.
هذا المكان هو بالفعل مكان جميل للرقص.
But didn't the teacher tell you?
لكن ألم يخبرك المعلم؟
This place now
هذا المكان الآن
is my changing room.
هي غرفة تغيير الملابس الخاصة بي.
Well then, I'll find another place.
حسنًا، سأجد مكانًا آخر.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Did I say you could leave?
هل قلت أنه يمكنك المغادرة؟
Firstly, this is a public classroom.
أولاً، هذا فصل دراسي عام.
I have the right to use it.
لدي الحق في استخدامه.
Secondly, you say this classroom
ثانيا، أنت تقول هذا الفصل الدراسي
is already your changing room,
هي بالفعل غرفة تغيير الملابس الخاصة بك،
but talk is cheap.
لكن الكلام رخيص.
I'll confirm with the teacher.
سأؤكد مع المعلم.
My family donates at least ten million
عائلتي تتبرع بما لا يقل عن عشرة ملايين
to this school every year.
لهذه المدرسة كل عام
Your scholarship comes from that.
المنح الدراسية الخاصة بك تأتي من ذلك.
Shouldn't you be grateful to me?
ألا يجب أن تكون ممتنًا لي؟
You think the teacher would favor you?
هل تعتقد أن المعلم سيفضلك؟
Who's there?
من هناك؟
So noisy.
مزعج جدا.
Lu Chengbei.
لو تشينغبي.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Can't I rest
لا أستطيع الراحة
in a public place.
في مكان عام.
I don't mean that.
أنا لا أقصد ذلك.
This place
هذا المكان
is indeed suitable as a changing room.
إنها بالفعل مناسبة كغرفة تغيير الملابس.
But she used my changing room.
لكنها استخدمت غرفة تغيير الملابس الخاصة بي.
Shouldn't we give her some
لا ينبغي لنا أن نعطيها بعض
punishment?
عقاب؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
You decide the punishment.
عليك أن تقرر العقوبة.
Beg me, and I'll help you.
توسل لي، وأنا سوف تساعدك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Do you remember how you
هل تتذكر كيف كنت
treated me back then?
تعاملني في ذلك الوقت؟
Jiang Shiqian,
جيانغ شيكيان,
I admit I was young and foolish,
اعترف اني كنت صغيره وغبيه
but now it's mine and Chengbei's engagement banquet.
لكنها الآن مأدبة خطوبة لي ولـChengbei.
Don't think about causing trouble,
لا تفكر في إثارة المشاكل
otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I won't let you off.
لن أسمح لك بالخروج.
The past is gone,
رحل الماضي،
but some things can't be let go.
لكن بعض الأشياء لا يمكن تركها.
You want to let me off,
تريد أن تتركني،
but I'm not ready to let you off.
لكنني لست مستعدًا للسماح لك بالرحيل.
What are you up to?
ما آخر ما توصلت اليه؟
Meng Xunmei,
منغ شونمي,
don't you think your life
ألا تعتقد أن حياتك
is like this evening dress?
هل مثل فستان السهرة هذا؟
Looks glamorous,
تبدو براقة،
but it's actually covered in bugs.
لكنها في الواقع مغطاة بالأخطاء.
Let me help you kill
اسمحوا لي أن أساعدك على القتل
all those bugs.
كل تلك الأخطاء.
Okay?
تمام؟
My dress!
ثوبي!
This is a limited edition.
هذه طبعة محدودة.
There's only one in the world.
هناك واحد فقط في العالم.
Next time,
المرة التالية،
it won't be just a dress.
لن يكون مجرد فستان.
Happy engagement.
خطوبة سعيدة.
♪Blue ocean♪
♪ المحيط الأزرق ♪
♪Stirring with the secrets of the wind♪
♪ التحريك بأسرار الريح ♪
♪Yet overheard by the moon♪
♪ لكن القمر سمعه ♪
♪Deep in the sea♪
♪في أعماق البحر♪
♪Your vast, gentle fins♪
♪ زعانفك الواسعة واللطيفة ♪
♪Are beyond reach♪
♪ بعيدة المنال ♪
♪Leaping forth♪
♪القفز للأمام♪
♪Like the moon embracing the tides♪
♪ مثل القمر يحتضن المد والجزر ♪
♪Unafraid of the distance between sea and sky♪
♪ غير خائف من المسافة بين البحر والسماء ♪
♪Fireflies dancing in the air converge towards you♪
♪ اليراعات المتراقصة في الهواء تتلاقى نحوك ♪
♪Just like I am enchanted by you♪
♪ مثلما أنا مسحور بك ♪
♪You come from the blue ocean♪
♪ لقد أتيت من المحيط الأزرق ♪
♪Not understanding my loneliness♪
♪لا أفهم وحدتي♪
♪While I wander the human world♪
♪ بينما أتجول في عالم البشر ♪
♪Collecting joy for you♪
♪ جمع الفرح بالنسبة لك ♪
♪How I wish that one day♪
♪ كم أتمنى ذلك يومًا ما ♪
♪You might inadvertently♪
♪ قد يحدث ذلك عن غير قصد ♪
♪Discover that I have always been residing♪
♪ اكتشف أنني كنت مقيمًا دائمًا ♪
♪In your eyes♪
♪ في عينيك ♪
♪You come from the blue ocean♪
♪ لقد أتيت من المحيط الأزرق ♪
♪Not understanding my loneliness♪
♪لا أفهم وحدتي♪
♪While I hide in the sea of people♪
♪ بينما أختبأ في بحر الناس ♪
♪Selling love for you♪
♪ بيع الحب لك ♪
♪If one day you could♪
♪إذا استطعت يومًا ما♪
♪Leap into the sky for me♪
♪اقفز إلى السماء من أجلي♪
♪You would surely find traces of my love for you♪
♪ ستجد بالتأكيد آثار حبي لك ♪
(The right of network communication of this work)
(حق شبكة الاتصال لهذا العمل)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)
(مملوكة حصريًا لشركة Shenzhen Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)